Guide to the Alliance for Progressive Action Records, 1990-2003 AIS.2004.15
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- "Yes Citizens for Police Accountability" Button (Box 13, Item 4)
- National Council for Urban Peace and Justice, Inc. Community Service Award to Citizens for Police Accountability, 1997 (Box 13, Item 5)
- Pittsburgh Black Media Federation Martin R. Delaney Award to Citizens for Police Accountability, 1997 (Box 13, Item 6)
- ACLU Greater Pittsburgh Chapter Marjorie H. Matson Civil Libertarian Award to Citizens for Police Accountability, February 15, 1998 (Box 13, Item 7)
- Fair Trade Campaign of Southwestern Pennsylvania and the North American Free Trade Agreement (Box 14)
- Oral History Interview Cassettes (Box 15, Item 1)
- Linda Wambaugh, United Mine Workers Food Bank, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Linda Wambaugh, United Mine Workers Local 6132 Charitable Trust (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Linda Wambaugh United Mine Workers Food Bank Notebook, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- United Mine Workers Stickers (Box 15, Folder 4)
- "National ERA March '80" Sash (Box 15, Item 2)
- Labor Solidarity March and Rally, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
- QEX Research (Box 16, Folder 1)
- WQED, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- QEX Legal File (Box 16, Folder 3)
- QEX Declarations (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Meeting Notes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- WNEU Nancy Hahn (Box 16, Folder 6)
- QED/QEX Related Notes (Box 16, Folder 7)
- QEX Plan B Swap Legislation, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Channel 40 Programming Quotes (Box 16, Folder 9)
- QEX Civil Law Suit (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Declaration Forms (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Leventhal, Senter and Therman Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Media Notes (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Handouts (Box 16, Folder 14)
- WQED/WQEX Media Coverage (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Petition to Deny Sale of WQED (Box 16, Folder 16)
- WQEX Plan B Swap, Letters Written to the FCC (Box 16, Folder 17)
- WQEX Plan B Swap, Conference Call Notes, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- QEX Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- QEX Plan B Swap, Save Pittsburgh Public Television Campaign (Box 16, Folder 20)
- James Roddey Clippings (Box 16, Folder 21)
- WQED, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- WQEX Press Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Asset Exchange Agreement between WQED Pittsburgh and Cornerstone Television, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Opposition to Petition to Delete Noncommercial Reservation, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Western Pennsylvania Christian Broadcast By-Laws (Box 16, Folder 26)
- QEX Mailings, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- WDUQ-FM, The Complex Society, George Miles "Explains" WQEX Swap, November 15, 1996 (Box 16, Cassette 1)
- Supplemental Showing, Cornerstone Broadcasting FCC File Balet, March 31, 1999 (Box 16, Cassette 2)
- Center for Social Studies Education (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Letters from Campaign Members regarding Stop WQEX Transfer (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Georgetown Law Center Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Petitions, Second Round (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Opposition of WQED to Petition to Deny, July 22, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Petition to Delete, July 9, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Opposition to Petition to Delete Noncommercial Reservation, July 5, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Cornerstone's Ammendments to FCC (Box 17, Folder 8)
- QEX Working File, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- WQED/FCC Hearing Information (Box 17, Folder 10)
- WQED/WPCB Swap Article, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Opposition to Delete Noncommercial Reservation, July 3, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Cornerstone Pleading to FCC, April 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Opposition to Petition to Deny, July 22, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- WQED Financial Reports, March 1997 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- WQED Public Inspection File Documents, October 30, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- QED Accountability Project Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 17)
- FCC Filing (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Asset Exchange Agreement Filed by QED with FCC, June 24, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Petition Filing, July 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Petition Revocation, July 1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Association of Local TV Stations, FCC Filing, July 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- WQED Privatization (Box 18)
- Grant Proposals, Pittsburgh Foundation, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Fast Track Jobs with Justice Report, August 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Jobs with Justice Stop Fast Track Proposal, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Ottinger Foundation Inquiry, July 2002 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Discount Grant, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Three Rivers Community Foundation Proposal, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Jobs with Justice Fast Track Grant, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Support Letter for FAT/UE Grant, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Three Rivers Grant, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Needmor Fund, June 28, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Tides Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11-13)
- Discount Inquiry, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- HERE Letter to Pat Coughlin, September 5, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Jobs With Justice Free Trade Area of the Americas Proposal, June 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Needmor Workplan and Budget Report, July-December 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Resist Grant, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Students in Solidarity Jobs With Justice Three Rivers Community Foundation Grant, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Tides Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Three Rivers Community Foundation Grant Application Guidelines, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Three Rivers Community Foundation Student Grant Fiscal Channel, April 2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program at Shelter Rock, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Three Rivers Community Foundation Grant Proposal, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Three Rivers Foundation, June 2001 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Ottinger Foundation Grant, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 26-28)
- Discount Proposal, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Needmor Grant, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 30-32)
- Peace Development Fund Inquiry, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Discount Proposal, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Needmor Proposal, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Unitarian Universal Veatch Grant, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Arca Foundation Proposal, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Discount Inquiry and Proposal, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 38-39)
- Funding Exchange, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 40-43)
- Grant Maker Information, Living Wage Campaign Fundraising, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Jewish Fund for Justice, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Needmor Grant, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 46-48)
- National Network of Grantmakers, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 49-51)
- Three Rivers Community Foundation Grant, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 52-55)
- Veatch Grant, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 56-58)
- Fund for a Just Society Proposal, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Ms. Foundation for Women Proposal, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Pitt Domestic Partner Report, May 2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Detroit Non-Profit Study, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Demographic Information (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Living Wage Campaign Poll Work, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Alaska Wilderness Project (Box 20, Folder 5)
- List of Parishes (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Esther Bush Letter, March 15, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Recent Demographics, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Living Wage Committee Labor Meeting, February 13, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Allegheny County Contracts by FTE's, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Allegheny County Contracts by Paid Amounts (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Allegheny Institute Study on Living Wage (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Allegheny County Community Support Program Committee Letter on Living Wage, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Valentines Day Living Wage Campaign Action, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- City of Pittsburgh, Tax Increment Financing Legislation (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Republican Convention Training, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Sanctuary by Fred E. Gustafson, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Worksheet on Livable Wage (Box 20, Folder 18)
- SEIU/PSAA (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Questions and Answers (Box 20, Folder 20)
- SEIU Living Wage Campaign Issues, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Proposed Allegheny County Living Wage Law, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Memo from Marc Cherna to Guy Tumolo, October 3, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Department of Human Services Plans and Budgets, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Living Wage Campaign Support Statements (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Questions and Legal Issues regarding Living Wage Legislation (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Living Wage Campaign District Work, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Anti-Living Wage Arguements (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Donald Short Petition and Letter (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Allegheny County Agency on Aging (Box 20, Folder 30)
- County Legislation Introduction, September 6, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Keystone Research Center, Living Wage Campaign County Service Contractor Report, November 2000 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- AFSCME Organizing (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Ferlo Memo, October 2000 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- National Association of Women Business Owners (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Record of Allegheny County Council Candidate Meetings (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Allegheny County Political Program (Box 20, Folder 37)
- City Council (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Regis Champ Remarks, March 1999 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Estate Tax, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Labor and Religion (Box 20, Folder 41)
- List of Non-Profit Human Service Providers (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Allegheny County Costs and Revenue (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Allegheny County Budget and Finance Committee, December 4, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Costs of Compliance (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Tumolo, Budget and Roddey (Box 20, Folder 46)
- MH/MR Compensation Project (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Kane Privatization (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Radio Commercials Schedule (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Citizens Review Board Petition and March Against Brutality List (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Citizens Review Board Public Hearing Registry List (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Community Training and Assistance Center Site Visit, Citizens for Police Accountability, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Cooperation Agreement (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Citizen Police Review Board Complaint Forms (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Strategy and Planning Meetings (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Citizen Police Review Board Meetings, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Steering Committee (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Draft Citizens Review Board Rules, March 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Sign-In Sheet (Box 21, Folder 11)
- National Related Information (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Press Releases (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Citizens for Police Accountability, Pittsburgh Police (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Events (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Citizens for Police Accountability General Information (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Citizens Review Board Ordinance (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Summary of Complaint Activity, July 15, 1998-December 31, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Linda Wambaugh, Citizens for Police Accountability (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Citizens Review Board Packet (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Citizen Police Review Board (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Pittsburgh Police, Media (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Action Alerts and Meetings (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Citizens for Police Accountability Funraising Letter (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Citizens Review Board (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Community Outreach Worker Forms (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Citizens Review Board Media Coverage (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Citizen Police Review Board (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Organizing Training, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
- APA organizing Survey (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Organizing for Our Future (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Three Rivers Community Fund Grant, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
- Tide Foundation Grant, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Unitarian Universal Funding, Pittsburgh, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Fundraising, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Three Rivers Community Fund, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Bridge Builders Foundation, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Funding Exchange, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Grant Proposals, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Funding Exchange, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- National Grantmakers Research (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Media for Grants, Living Wage Committee (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Mellon Collaboration Proposal, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Three Rivers Community Fund Proposal, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Partnership for Democracy Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Resist Proposal, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Resist Grant, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Three Rivers Community Fund Training Grant, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Resist Grant Attachments, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Veatch at Shelter Rock (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Heinz Foundation (Box 22, Folder 22)
- APA Office Files (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
- Expenses (Box 22, Folder 25)
- The Needmor Fund (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Foundation Lists (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Fundraising Proposal Components (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Pittsburgh Foundations (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Living Wage Campaign Fundraising (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Fundraising Information (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Free Trade Area of the Americas and the North American Free Trade Agreement (Box 23)